mercuriurval.com 2018-09-10

# Privacy - Mercuri Urval

## Privacy Policy

This website is operated by Mercuri Urval ("we" or "us"). **By using and visiting our website and by submitting your personal information to us you agree to us using your personal information as set out in this privacy policy.**

If you want to know about how we use cookies please click here.

We respect the privacy of users of our website and recognise that when you choose to provide us with information about yourself, you trust us to act in a responsible manner with that information. This privacy policy contains important information about how we use your personal information.

**What information do we collect?**

At times we may request that you voluntarily supply us with personal information. Generally this information is requested when you want us to provide you with information.

We may gather the following information about you:

  * Name
  * Email address
  * Telephone number
  * IP address (a unique identifier for your computer or other device)
  * Mobile device ID

Information provided by you in relation to submitting a job application to us (this may include sensitive personal information e.g. ethnic origin)

**How do we use it?**

We will use this information in the following ways:

  * to provide you with information that you have requested e.g. a newsletter, job subscriptions;
  * to respond to specific queries you may raise regarding Mercuri Urval and its operating companies;
    * to provide you with better ways of accessing information from this website;
    * to process and consider your job application;

For how we use your information that is collected using cookies and similar technologies please see the "Cookies" here.

**Do we pass your information to third parties?**

We may send your personal information to other group companies, affiliates and third parties to help us process your personal information for the purposes set out in this policy.

We may disclose your personal information if we or any of our assets are the subject of a sale or similar corporate transaction. We will ensure that the third parties who receive your personal information are required to keep it confidential.

We may disclose personal information to third parties when we reasonably believe we are required by law, and in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual unlawful or otherwise prohibited activities, including, but not limited to, fraud.

**How do we use your information for marketing?**

We will only provide information to you that you have asked for via the website.

**Where do we send your information?**

We are a global company and therefore we may transfer your personal information to countries around the world including the US and other countries outside Europe. We will, where necessary, put in place appropriate safeguards to ensure your information is protected.

**How long do we keep your information?**

We will keep your information for a reasonable period for the purposes set out above.
